<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Glasswall CDR Platform</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Glasswall CDR Platform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/0_introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/0_introduction/</guid><description>Introduction This project creates a deployment that is able to process GBs of unique files. Implementation should pick up these files and process them via Rebuild engine in a deployment based on 2 ESXi servers. Architecture elements Workflow cluster Worker cluster Load balancer Monitoring 3 Hard disks (source, evidence and target) Flow diagram Data mapping The Metadata module The Metadata_Service class manages the creation and updating of the metadata.</description></item><item><title>Deploy CDR Plugin in AWS</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/1_how_to_deploy_cdr_plugin_aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/1_how_to_deploy_cdr_plugin_aws/</guid><description>Deploying CDR Plugin on AWS Use latest CDR Plugin AMI. AMI ID can be found in github actions: https://github.com/filetrust/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/actions/workflows/cdr-plugin.yml Login to AWS Console Navigate to AWS &amp;gt; AMIs Search for the AMI with specific ID from the first step (make sure you are in correct region) From AMIs workspace click on specific AMI &amp;gt; Choose Launch Set instance type to t3.2x.large and extend storage to at least 50GB (in case you are planning to test large data sets set storage to higher value) Add any tags if needed Add security group if needed (for CDR by default nothing additional should be set) Click on Review and Launch Select Create or use existing key pair [Note: Key is not needed for SSH at the moment] Wait for instance to be initialized (~10 minutes) and use public IP to access CDR Plugin VM SSH to your instance (password will be shared): ssh -L 8002:127.</description></item><item><title>Deploy CDR Plugin in ESXi</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/2_how_to_deploy_cdr_plugin_esxi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/2_how_to_deploy_cdr_plugin_esxi/</guid><description>Offline deployment flow using OVAs Deploying Workflow Cluster OVA Login to VMWare ESXi console
Select Virtual machines &amp;gt; Create / Register VM &amp;gt; Deploy a virtual machine from OVF or OVA file Browse and import OVA (downloaded from S3 bucket) Leave default data storage
Set VM adapter.
Note: On your ESXI Server, make sure the network adapter is set correctly and created VM is assigned to the corresponding adapter.</description></item><item><title>End to End Workflow on AWS</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/3_end_to_end_workflow_aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/3_end_to_end_workflow_aws/</guid><description>Parts of the End to End Workflow - AWS Worker cluster = Glasswall SDK AMI Workflow cluster = CDR Plugin AMI Prerequisites Deploy Glasswall SDK VM
You can reuse already deployed GW SDK VMs (IPs) You can use and you should use more than one GW SDK VM (depending on amount of data you are testing) Deploy CDR Plugin VM
You can use this video as a reference SSH to your CDR Plugin VM</description></item><item><title>End to End Workflow on ESXI</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/4_end_to_end_workflow_esxi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/4_end_to_end_workflow_esxi/</guid><description>Parts of the End to End Workflow - ESXI Worker cluster = Glasswall SDK OVA Workflow cluster = CDR Plugin OVA Glasswall Desktop OVA On previous pages you can find how to deploy each of these 3 as a separate VMs. Have them ready and have their IPs available. All 3 VMs should be in the same Network, as that will enable their offline, mutual communication.
Deploy Glasswall SDK VM Deploy CDR Plugin VM Deploy Glasswall Desktop VM Within VM: Update hosts file with Glasswall SDK ip and CDR Plugin VM ip, by running sudo nano /etc/hosts and update IP addresses: Next to gw-sdk.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/5_faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/5_faq/</guid><description>CONTENT How to download rebuild file? How to remove files form HD2 right after all files are processed? How to change CDR Plugin VM, volume size to accommodate more testing files? How to check which CDR Plugin version I am using? How to check which GW SDK version I am using? How to access Elastic and Kibana dashboards? Where to find data sets for testing? How to count the number of files being processed or created in HD2/HD3 directly from CDR VM?</description></item><item><title>How to start?</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/6_how_to_start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/6_how_to_start/</guid><description>Wiki pages to refer to:
FAQ How to use end to end workflow ESXI How to use end to end workflow AWS Helpful videos:
How to deploy CDR Plugin VM How to ssh to CDR Plugin VM How to run tests on CDR Plugin VM</description></item><item><title>New workflows</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/7_additional_workflows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/7_additional_workflows/</guid><description>CONTENT 1. Retry workflow 2. Uploading the zip file via URL 3. Setting the number of threads for pre processing 4. Checking the CDR plugin/ GW SDK version 5. Processed File Dashboard 6. Threat Analysis Dashboard 1. Retry workflow Context:
After running CDR F2F processing of specific scenario, rerun the scenario for failed files. Steps:
Run CDR F2F processing (CLEAR &amp;gt; LOAD &amp;gt; START) After processing is done verify the number and context of failed files Rerun CDR F2F processing (START) Verify the number and context of failed files Goal:</description></item><item><title>Remote Storage Mount</title><link>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/remote_storage_mount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filetrust.github.io/cdr-plugin-folder-to-folder/docs/remote_storage_mount/</guid><description>S3 Mount Download rclone curl https://rclone.org/install.sh | sudo bash Run rclone config Enter below values n/s/q&amp;gt; - n name&amp;gt; - &amp;lt;remote_name&amp;gt; ( any name ) Storage - 4 provider - 1 env_auth - 1 and give aws access key and secret key region - &amp;lt;blank&amp;gt; endpoint - &amp;lt;blank&amp;gt; location_constraint - &amp;lt;blank&amp;gt; acl - 2 ( depends on use case ) server_side_encryption - 2 sse_kms_key_id - 2 storage_class - 2 ( depends on use case ) Edit advanced config?</description></item></channel></rss>